NOAM ACKERMAN

Frontend Developer

About Myself

I'm Noam Ackerman, a frontend developer experienced in React, Next.js, JavaScript, TypeScript, CSS, and more. I'm not just a coder but also a versatile musician and visual artist. I thrive on challenges, I'm a quick learner, problem solver, and a highly creative individual. I value healthy and productive communication.

Experience

Flare - Linkedin link

Frontend Engineer

2024 - present

- I collaborated with numerous teams to deliver data-driven features from Figma to production for complex online funnels, marketing acquisition pages and web apps for attorneys and customers.
- I developed with technologies including Next.js, React, TypeScript, Tailwind, Git, Builder.io, React Testing Library, Jest/Vitest and more.
- I focused on clean, reusable code by creating reusable components, custom hooks and shared utility functions.
- I contributed to frontend guild initiatives, including monorepo convention guidelines and the company's new design system.

PlayTracker - Website link

Freelancer Developer

2023 - 2024

- I researched gaming platform and games APIs through official docs, third-party libraries, and network sniffing.
- I designed solutions for retrieving player profiles and stats across platforms.
- I developed interactive user interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

Nosto Solutions - Website link

Frontend Developer

2021 - 2023

- I developed dynamic, responsive merchant interfaces used daily by thousands, using ReactJS, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, and jQuery.
- I owned features from Figma to production, managing Jira tickets and resolving bugs through merchant site investigations.
- I designed UI mockups, wireframes, and improved UX.
- I initiated and guided a new team workflow, created documents to boost productivity, and optimized project management efficiency.

Portfolio

Check out my Portfolio at - noamackerman.com

Education

Front-end, React and responsive web development

SheCodes USA, 2021

Epic React - Course for Advanced React

Kent C. Dodds, 2023

Online Courses for TypeScript and for NodeJS

2023

Contact

+972505954084

developer.noam@gmail.com

www.noamackerman.com

github.com/noam-ackerman

in <u>linkedin.com/in/noam-</u> <u>ackerman/</u>

Skills

ReactJS & NextJS

JavaScript

TypeScript

CSS & Tailwind & Sass

HTML

Git

Firebase

Responsive Development

Jest & React-testing-library

Tools

VS code

Figma

Photoshop

Jira

Slack

Builder.io (CMS)

Languages

Hebrew - Native

English - Fluent